The City of London.
Uuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuuhuuhuhuuhuuhuhuuhuuhn.
You.
Ahhhhhhhhhh.
The End.
Emergency!
We got a tip-off here about a bank
robbery happening in Poki City?
Yeah?
Well, good luck with that, pal.
And let me know if you capture him!
You're not hearing me!
This ain't no ordinary robber!
It's him! Gasp back! What?
You gotta sit back up!
We need a squad!
Don't make that two squads!
Pronto!
To hell with that!
I'll fit you a platoon!
A struggle over resources.
In the end, that's all
life is. Kane. Move it!
We all move things from there
to here from here to there
Every person alive is obsessed with their
own little piece of the
pie ain't that right?
Not at all the life.
We have the result of hard work
That's the same thing.
You just happen to have enough
resources in your town to pull it off!
What you don't realize is you took all
you have from other people in places now?
I don't think I'm criticizing you.
Like I said, life's a
struggle over resources.
Men, women, old folks, little
brats, it don't matter.
Anyone can dance the dance.
Kane,
don't you think it's
time you did something
about your nasty habit of
stealing in these petty,
sneaky ways?
Ripping people off all
sneaky-like doesn't suit me.
Swindling's also not my style.
I just never thought people should
engage in that kind of stuff.
That being said,
legit businesses are so
much worse. Why is that?
Because I like seeing the faces
of the people I'm stealing from.
I love their astonished expressions as
they watch me walk off with their goods.
Come on, fellas,
where's the struggle if we don't get the
benefit of being face-to-face like this?
Boss!
We're ready to start!
Alright.
Let's go.
This place is finished.
People say once Gasback
tears through a bank,
he doesn't leave so much as a single
weed standing in his wake well that
depends on how you look at it sir if
we don't resist at least we can walk
out of here with our lives come on
there's no need to cry look if this
wasn't gas back at all but that bash
the stampede guy the humanoid typhoon
heck you could forget all about weeds that
lunatic wouldn't leave any of us with even
a single hair on our
heads yeah that's true
oh I see you're saying this is better than
being attacked by that
guy we're lucky that
it's gas back we're
lucky that it's gas back
I'm lucky that it's gas
back we're lucky that
it's gas back that was the The last piece.
I really like the look on those faces.
Now I'm happy.
We ready yet, Kane?
This is the last one.
This is farewell.
I really hate to, but we've got to split.
We're leaving you here, Gasback.
I guess that wasn't an accident.
That shot was a message to let you know
this is the last job we're doing with you.
Oh?
We're fed up with your crap.
All you do is chase down the big
scores like some grade-A moron.
We bust our asses to steal cash,
and you dump it into the next job.
Just like you were gonna
do this time, right?
I thought that was the whole point, Kane.
That's what a rubber lives for.
Why even bother with this if
you don't take it seriously?
Give me a break.
If I wanted to work seriously,
I'd have a real job.
Yeah, that's right.
Now I get it.
You pulled these other two airheads
over to your way of thinking.
All we want is to live the good life
while doing as little work as possible.
So as of today, you're no longer our boss.
Is that so?
Well, it just works out that I've been
getting fed up with your petty nature, too.
I have to ask,
wouldn't you be surprised
if I told you the
police were tipped off
about tonight's job?
Don't worry, we're gonna
take all of the cash with us.
And we'll blow your corpse to smithereens!
If you think you can actually
take me down, then give it a shot.
I really thought you
would have noticed by now.
Cause I noticed it's a piece of cake
to kill you when you're unarmed.
Goodbye, gas back!
If you pull that trigger,
you'll be the one to die.
No, you're bluffing.
Why don't you find out?
You son of a...
What do you know?
Just like I was saying.
Now, I don't know what's going on,
but it looks like luck's on my side.
Calm down
I am calm
enough to be able
to clear your brains out in one shot
Please don't. Please.
I was wrong.
You have to forgive me. I'm sorry.
You did the worst possible
thing you could have done to me.
You disgraced my robbery!
My robbery, jackass!
Now what to do?
Because if I blow your brains out,
I won't be able to watch your soul
drain out of your lifeless face!
You're on my donut!
Hurry, hurry up and move your foot!
You gotta hurry!
Three second rule!
My poor crumbly donut...
That is the meanest thing
anyone's ever done to me!
Why do you want to ruin
other people's food?
I can't eat a pile of smashed up crumbs!
You want to live through
this, then sit your butt down!
You guys are the ones who barfed
in here and dragged me into
this when I was about to eat
my donut in peace and quiet.
You tied me up and left me on the floor.
Did you hit your head when we tied
you up, or are you always like this?
I just want to replace my donut.
Shut up, if you're going
to keep getting in my way.
My donut.
What is wrong with you?
Get off of me, you idiot.
Give me a replacement donut.
I demand a replacement donut. Give me one.
Give me one now.
Huh?
Can't be.
According to the Zippanese, a grudge
over food is a frightening thing.
Can it?
I'm still trying to think about what
I can steal from you people right now.
Let's bash the stampede!
Help!
We're all gonna die!
Shut up!
Keep talking nonsense,
you'll be the first to go.
No, we're not.
We're dead! No!
No!
Seems like you're busy mucking
up the works here, pal.
The hell's your game, anyway?
You saved me first, then you saved them.
What do any of us have
to do with you, huh?
What's your business here?
It's just... well...
Ain't it better if we all live?
Can't believe I'm hearing that from
the mouth of the humanoid typhoon.
Well, you know...
I don't think it's a good idea.
Giving away something for free,
even if it's just a single life.
It's against the way of this world.
Maybe, but you can't just constantly
steal everything from everyone.
Look, once a die's been cast,
there's no going back. Huh?
And you rolled someone
else's die here today, Vash.
I hope you won't regret what you've done.
See you around.
That's a little overkill, don't you think?
Don't tell me you hit the plant!
Nah, it'll be fine.
See, they got backups.
You should worry about that.
We got a big problem! See ya!
I'm the mastermind?
Clad in a long red coat that
flutters in the burning sand,
he's the devil's messenger.
A man known to reduce the
most prosperous cities to ash.
Vash, the stampede.
An outlaw with 60 billion
double dollars on his head.
The man known horizon to
horizon as the humanoid typhoon.
getting older hasn't changed him one bit
he kept a low profile for a while but
now he's got a hundred million double-dollar
bounty on his head this morning it's
not 300 million 300 million damn I might
go after him myself I dare you you'll
just come back in a pine box why you think
you can do it no way wouldn't even try
That's the gaudiest
thing I've ever seen. Mr.
Kepler reorganized Maka
City's plant twenty years ago.
Took him five years to build it.
Looks like he's proud of that.
Proud enough to build a bronze
statue honoring himself.
Wow, sounds like he's gonna
be a real joy to deal with.
I'm sure we'll be fine.
We got a gift for him.
People love gifts.
Yeah, good point.
And on top of that, it's
bigger than our usual ones.
Hey, ladies, if you're not busy, what say
you join us for an alcoholic beverage?
No, thank you.
We are busy. Wait.
Hold on a second.
Couldn't hurt you to spend
a little time with us.
We got a lot to offer
Hold up, what are you doing there?
Yeah,
sorry about that guy
looks like you started off
with a lousy greeting
didn't you what's going on?
Why is the town packed with
so many bounty hunters anyway?
You mean you haven't
seen the posters whoa?
This is gas back.
We got a rumor circling that he's planning
to strike here in Maka City So mr.
Kepler's gathering bounty
hunters instead of bodyguards
Now it makes sense.
I know why headquarters
told us to come all the
way out here to confirm
the insurance contract?
The payout for that bronze statue is
five billion double dollars five billion.
We hit the burner deli insurance
society are on the verge of extinction
It's my turn!
enjoy your red kid I
Want some smoked Thomas
That's great, but you need
to wait your turn in line.
Just hurry and give us what we want.
Hey, are you gonna pay for that meat?
Make it smoked Thomas and sausage
There sure are a lot of bad-mannered
idiots riding with us today.
Gasback's just a worthless old thief.
He's too old to even know how
to rob a place right anymore.
Three hundred million double dollars
is a hell of an easy payday for us.
Don't flap your mouth.
Let your guard down.
He could turn the tables on you.
Well,
if you're scared, buddy,
wouldn't it be better for your
constitution to hop off the ship right now?
Am I right, brother?
Are you a chick?
Hey, let me see your face for a sec.
Huh? Don't touch.
Ah, I found a little birdie in
this dingy place. Traveling alone?
You hungry?
Move.
Come here, lady.
Hey, I found her first.
So what do you say you'd
travel with me, princess?
I can be one rockin' good time.
Whoa, that's one fine look.
I don't touch me.
Don't even try.
Sounds like a challenge
Didn't you hear me when I said
don't touch me you're acting like
you've never seen a woman before
you guys like virgins or what?
You got a lot of spunk in you
lady See, I like that in my women.
In fact, it makes what I had in
mind that much more interesting.
See, because when I force
you to do what I want you...
Whipping out your knife on
this ship is just bad manners.
Move it!
It's too late to apologize, you bitch!
She kicked him twice!
Don't you screw with me!
I'll kick you some more if you want.
Not before I shut your mouth!
Your leg's got a bad habit of kicking.
Nice, now get her
shoulders and pin her down.
Got it.
Excuse me, guys.
Aren't you using a knife earlier?
I think you might have dropped
it over here somewhere.
See, it's just that I could
really go for some of that.
Smoked Thomas me but I
forgot to bring a knife.
I was hoping you guys
would let me borrow yours.
I've killed more idiots like you
than I can even remember to count.
Now hold still.
Just what I was looking for.
This is the one that your friend there
dropped earlier when he got saddlebagged.
Right.
Look, I just need it for a little bit.
I want to scrape some of this Thomas me.
You don't mind do?
Do you?
I do. What?
That sucks.
Now I can't eat my little snack.
Whatever.
Hey, idiot. Yeah?
Hope you're ready to die! Bye!
Oh, no! I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
I apologize. I do.
Please forgive me.
Get off of me. Come on.
You don't have to be like that.
I apologize.
I said get off of me, you bastard.
Just settle down, big guy.
I said I was sorry.
I'll give you now.
Get off.
Thanks.
What a moron. Which one?
Both, I guess. No doubt.
Uh-huh.
Neither of you are getting away
with this crap, you hear me?
You hear me?
This is bad.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Is he gonna shoot?
The first thing I'm gonna do is make this
chick pay for not letting me touch her.
I'm gonna put you through hell.
Cry all you want.
I ain't ever gonna let you off the hook.
You're gonna cry and cry
and when the tears dry up.
I'm gonna make you cry some more.
I'll teach you to make me angry
Which means you're my slave
now redhead you hear me?
On your knees!
I said on your knees!
Do what I say!
I changed my mind.
You really shouldn't make
such a racket, fellas,
and you shouldn't fire
your gun on the ship!
Oh enough with the applause
you're embarrassing me!
Those guys fired shots, didn't they?
From what?
But I understand not firing on
the ship is one of the core rules,
and we gotta follow!
the rules out here now, don't we?
Right, but we can still
be tolerant of them.
Rules are rules!
On this ship, we got a zero-tolerance
policy for jackals like you! Here!
Your guns and crap!
Here!
We put cool and water in there
too, so you better appreciate that!
Also, here's a souvenir for you!
Maybe some gypsies or scavengers
will pick you up out here.
Well, I'll leave you ladies to it.
This palace screams new money, doesn't it?
Yeah, even his guards are
pretentious and extravagant.
Thank you so much for waiting.
I'm Mr Kepler.
Oh, hello.
I know you're busy, so
thanks for meeting us.
You're from some insurance company?
Yes, but before we get to that...
We know it's not much, but... Oof!
Oof! Oof!
What are you doing? I'm just...
All clear.
The package isn't a threat.
Excellent.
You're dismissed.
I apologize.
We're in a state of
high alert around here.
Oh.
Perfect.
So, you're reviewing the contract.
Why's that?
Oh, well...
We decided on the amount
after spending considerable
time to explain the
contents to your company.
You don't doubt our report, do you?
No, of course not.
But it was still under construction
when we assessed its value.
Also,
the numbers you gave
us before and the ones
you gave us after don't
quite seem to match up.
It stands as a symbol of this town.
We can't put a price on it.
Yes, it sure is incredible.
Then we shouldn't have a problem here.
By rights, I'd want insurance?
Not just for the bronze
statue, but for the plant, too.
Everyone in this town, myself
included, depends on it for survival.
It's kind of like you
sit here earning money
without ever having to do a single thing.
Well, sorry about this, but
it's not possible for the plant.
We can't cover that whole entity.
With property insurance, you see,
our company just doesn't have.
I understand, but I insist the amount
for the statue remain the same.
Don't we have to assess its
value before we apply it?
Our company is the stingiest
one in the insurance industry.
But they thought five
billion was appropriate.
Nothing we do here now will
make a bit of difference.
We can't change their minds, is that so?
Millie, they didn't send us
here to do the assessment.
The only reason we're here is to.
to serve as their look-outs so that they
won't have to pay the insurance money.
I get it,
but don't you think it'd
be impossible to steal that
big ol' thing with so many
people around all the time?
It's not only a matter of
it being stolen or not.
If Gas Back shows up under these
circumstances, imagine what would happen.
There goes five billion!
Millie we absolutely have
to protect this that is if
we don't want to depend on
unemployment insurance Roger
Hey, hold up.
Come on, let's chat a little bit.
Who and I didn't get a
chance to talk on the ship?
I'd like to get to know you.
Back off.
We got nothing to talk about.
What?
That is so cold.
Where are you from?
And you didn't even tell me your name.
If I didn't say thanks for
saving me, then thanks.
Now, why are you following
me like a lost dog?
I felt our meeting was
nothing short of destiny.
Don't tell me you didn't feel it, too.
Just stop pestering me.
But it sent the hairs on the
back of my neck into a frenzy.
Come on, I know you also felt it.
It went like this.
I've had enough of you.
Look, the least you can
do is tell me your name.
Are you okay?
This is an allergic reaction.
It happens when I touch idiots like men.
What?
Even a good-looking stud like me?
Good-looking?
I swear all men are the same.
Then maybe this was the wrong town
for you to make your destination.
It's chock-full of idiot men.
Bounty hunters mostly.
Don't go confusing me
with the likes of them.
Back off.
We aren't inside a sand steamer anymore.
I'd still really like to know your name.
You're a dead man!
I'm gonna kill you!
What's the matter, Meryl?
I just saw something,
but it was an illusion.
It was an illusion, I know.
Hey, Cain.
What did I say?
Don't come out without my permission.
I was just wondering if he's coming here.
What do you think?
There's no chance just making you
lose everything would satisfy him.
It...
it was all that I had.
Just when I had finally
put together a good life.
Am I next, Armachio?
Maybe we should just run away.
And leave everything I've built I have
the power I've wanted my whole life.
I'm not gonna let him take that away
No!
Great, please fire, man!
This is my job.
Sorry, boy.
Money!
Pay us the rest of the money you owe us!
Can't we pay them stallments?
You said you'd pay!
You're not gonna get away with this!
I tell you, you're one hell
of a money gun, my man!
Gotta be sheer luck to
find you when I did!
Why?
Why won't you take my bill?
You're in our way.
If you want to die, there's
a cemetery close by.
Please, rape this bill.
Huh?
Bobs, look.
Can't believe I didn't take
that big old cross of yours.
Come to think of it, that was the second
time I gave something for nothing.
How generous.
You deserve some kind of reward.
I just want you to feel you owe me, as
I got some big jobs planned after this.
I'll return the favor for you saving me.
But like I told you at the start, I'm not
gonna be part of your robberies at all.
I'm only your bodyguard,
nothing more. Yeah, yeah,
but with that monster
of a firearm you carry,
don't act all smug like
you've never done a bad thing.
I may not look like it,
but I'm a man of the cloth.
All I am is a part of the
life and death of people.
That's why I fire a gun. Ha!
Never heard of a man of
the club being like that!
Going out for dinner?
The two of us could go together.
Hey, lady!
The chick.
Check out that swagger!
I don't think she's
looking back at any of us.
Why won't you just stop
following me? What?
We were on the same sand
steamer to the same town.
That's got to count for something,
destiny, fate, whatever.
We should cherish things like that.
Then don't you have more in common
with those losers than with me?
You only came here to claim the bounty
on Gasback's head too, didn't you?
What do you mean?
You didn't.
No way.
I only came here to meet you, Amelia.
Want to tell me how you know my name
read it off the ends guest register
We're staying at the same in it's more
like the same One
more
time back off. It's my turn.
I'm winning this throw already
What about me? Screw you.
This is my game.
What do you know?
Looks like I'm the one who's
gonna take it, suckers.
Bingo!
Cheaters, I'm quitting.
Cash first.
Folk over my money.
What are you talking about?
Is it just the two of you?
Nah, just me.
How hard is it to get a
quiet table at this joint?
Malone.
Maybe two seats at the bar?
Just one seat. Oh, Nido!
What are you doing here?
We got two open seats!
I can't believe it!
A couple of my friends are here!
And they got two available seats!
We should go sit with them!
Barkeep, find me a seat, would ya?
Looks like they got the only open two!
Cheers!
Number 8!
So it's quite the coincidence
you're after gas back, too, Amelia.
That is so cool.
Now, if you're considering during this
treacherous time getting life insurance,
I just want to let you know
we've got a really simple plan.
Thanks, I'm fine.
Life insurance just makes for bad luck.
Besides, this chick's a strong one.
so what's your deal huh?
did you come here for the bounty like
every other questionable character?
no i just came out here for the
sightseeing is that the honest truth?
yeah you're not gonna drop yourself
into this gas back business are you?
well don't give me that smirk even
if that's not why you're here this
statue crisis is big time we don't
need the humanoid typhoon running
Would you mind just getting out
of town and leaving us alone?
What?
Are you asking me to bail on our reunion?
You know as well as I do you're
just a magnet for trouble.
You don't have to spit the venom, Meryl.
I'm just here for some lame sightseeing.
I know I can't trust you.
You've probably already gotten into
trouble since you've been here.
Don't tell me you had gas back.
No, I just got into town today.
I don't know anything.?
And what are you two ladies doing here?
Seems like a lifetime since
last I had the pleasure
of your company we had
a change in immediate
priorities Thanks to
company orders here on
business lucky you she's
as serious as ever. Yep.
That's dependable Meryl go on say
what you want to say. I don't care.
I just wish you would leave us alone
Because after this job is over we're gonna
have to get back to following you around
wherever you end up
traipsing off to Next so
you insurance girls are
like stalkers stalkers.
No, we just follow you.
We don't kill you or anything
What are you doing?
Let go!
You're probably just playing dumb,
trying to stay in town, but
I won't let that happen.
This is not cool, not cool!
Let go, please!
Come on!
You're not being such a baby!
Bash! Bash! The Stampede!
Do you not give a flying crap
if this town goes into a panic?
Keep in mind, you wouldn't benefit
from it if it did, so quirk it!
Jeez!
Ow!
How dare you!
How dare you treat Vash
the Stampede like this!
Do you know my reputation?
You'll pay for this!
Are you kidding that
skinny bonehead? No way!
He'd blow away on his stupid boots!
No way!
Hey, come on!
Vash the vengeful monster,
not a chick's boy toy!
Well, maybe he's got something wrong in
that stance, talking about his nonsense.
Or he's doing cosplay!
He's dressed just like
the dead wanted poster!
Here I am!
Vash the stampede!
Okay, okay, you're the real vash.
I don't think he looks like him at all!
Come back after you've worked
on your impassion! Thank you!
Thank you very much!
I'm a bonafide hit!
No, you're a bonafide jackass!
Stop!
I'm a legendary outlaw
with a bounty on his hand!
Stop!
I'm so scared!
There's a limit to recklessness.
Gas-back is no match for Vash.
As things stand now, we're screwed.
Look at that.
Things just standing there, arms
wide open, begging for me to take it.
God, he ugly-faced
piece of junk like that.
You really gonna waste your
talents trying to steal it?
I gotta pay its owner back for something.
Took me a while to find the old boy,
but I plan to make this robbery
one for the record books.
The best one in all the
days I put into thieving.
Instead of grabbing fruit
off the tree when it's green,
you should wait it out as long as you can.
And wait, and wait.
Then, when it's as ripe as it'll ever
be, you grab that sucker and pull.
The action looks the same, but
the taste is completely different.
Same thing with robbery.
You reach for your target when
it's ripened to its greatest point.
This man will experience a despair that he
couldn't have begun to
imagine in his life.
I mean,
there's almost no point to robbery if
it doesn't cause at least a little pain.
The world's greatest robbery
is out there waiting.
And that is exactly where I'm heading.
I'm hoping you'll come with
me on this journey, buddy.
Our contract does say you'll be with
me at least until we get to his place.
I've gotten in debt to a man with
some serious issues, haven't I?
You said you don't agree
much, but here you are again.
Climb the hell off my ass.
You know I love the
atmosphere in this joint.
Such a kind word you got.
Just one shot from that.
Was you even listening?
I said LeBron's statue
has had the troubles.
Gas back and the insurance.
Yeah!
Oh my God, but he's all right.
Oh, of course.
Gaspac is the...
Toilet.
Catch you later!
Yo!
So, uh, what did you say?
Like I said,
that Brian statue is in your troubles.
Gaspac is the insurance.
What did you say to me, you cow?
Fine, I'll repeat myself.
You can't get women and
money and stuff like that?
By forcing yourself on those things,
Are you being sarcastic when
you're calling me a genius?
Or am I hearing you wrong?
Oh, you're hearing me wrong.
Let me clear the whole thing up for you.
I'll whisper in your ear, okay?
You are a shitbag.
You bitch!
Fine!
I wouldn't mind taking a
piece of this action, brother.
Stay out of this, Tubby!
I want that chick behind you!
So is it me?
Or did a fight just
break out in the house?
You're a marshal!
Why don't you do something? Why?
This is what I came here to see!
Where'd that cow go?
You're a dead woman!
Could I ask everyone to calm down?
Please?
This is supposed to be a fun place for us
all to just relax and have a few drinks,
so why don't we put our
fists up and do that?
What do you say?
Here we go!
I'm done with you bitch!
What the hell?
My bullets, where are they?
You bring it up!
Come on, give them back now!
All right, this way,
so we'll see you later.
No problem.
Great catching up.
You two, have a good night.
It must be tough being an insurance agent.
Would you let me off I can walk just
pocket your pride Amelia can't you tell I'm
not even trying to touch you or anything
I'm saving that for when we get into bed?
Hey dummy did you know that
gas back was he was almost
caught before he was cornered
and almost captured once before,
something like 20 years ago.
Interesting.
His robber buddies almost killed him, but
then some stupid moron let him get away.
Good God, it's beyond freaking annoying.
I always wonder if he'd have died then?
how many people could
have lived their lives?
without feeling sorrow or pain.
That guy that let him go was
his accomplice, you know?
That guy makes me sick.
Could it be that maybe he took
something precious from you?
My money's on.
He stole your first kiss.
You bastard, you drink my booze!
What did a guy like you come to a
stinking town like this for anyway,
if not to nail gas back?
Beats me.
Kind of like I'm chasing
the die I cast, I guess.
Huh?
Um, I'll put it like this.
You and me, we fell into a love paradise.
Oh, I said to...
Oh, no!
Just let me know if you're gonna puke.
I'll be fine. That's great.
Then you and I should get our
little tails back to our love nest!
Yeah! Stop!
You better put me down!
No, please don't do it on me!
What is that, Mom?
It's a precious secret, sweetie.
What kind of secret?
The kind I'll tell you about someday
when you grow up to be a young woman.
Mom! Mom! No!
Amelia, I'm sorry, baby.
I'm sorry I won't be able to be.
I won't be.
I won't be with you as you grow up.
That precious secret.
Do you remember?
I'll tell you now.
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Mom...
It wouldn't meet!
Hey, go easy on that drinking.
You want to be able to
function in our hour of peril.
Look who's talking, you
good-for-nothing lawman.
Let's get you back to your office.
No, I'm the goddamn marshal.
I'll keep patrolling.
Things going smoothly, fellas?
Everything's good.
For a town this size,
I'd say this plant could provide power for
at least the next several hundred years.
Amazing.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
A billion double dollars.
Get up.
It's time to go.
It's gas back!
Cannot confirm ID.
Leave premises immediately.
If you do not leave within two
minutes, you will be eliminated.
If you have weapons,
you will be eliminated.
Oh, shut up, you annoying
pieces of chakra!
Eliminate.
Now that's what I call a partner.
That's a very strange
method you're using there.
It'll fry you like bacon instantly.
You want to break through it,
you need ten lives in the wings.
Ready, boss!
Machio's factory was destroyed?
He's asking you for shelter.
Okay.
You can let him in.
Did you hear that gas back
hit Dennis City last night?
Are you kidding me?
Bang!
You got me!
We're the best!
We just killed Gaspack!
I begged you out!
Now let's go start my
mission to order time!
What are you doing, Vash?
Good to see you today.
You look pretty good for pounding
as much booze as you did last night.
We got some good news this
morning which helped considerably.
We heard Gaspack attacked a factory
in Denna instead of striking here.
Isn't that great?
He what?
I bet he wasn't even after
this town in the first place.
It might be expensive,
but I thought it was strange for him to
go after such a gaudy piece of garbage.
Don't you think you're being
a bit mouthy about that?
At any rate, we have to
contact headquarters.
We'll see you later.
Bye-bye.
So, all that stuff about him
targeting this town was just rumors?
We got fooled.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
To a different town to get
some information on gas back.
Targeting this town might have just
been a rumor he started himself.
He may be a bad guy, but he's a smart one.
I don't want to discount that.
I don't know if he would have...
No, wait.
You're right.
There's no way he targeted
a remote town like this.
Bye.
Maybe we'll catch up again somewhere.
You're a crummy actor.
You still think Gasback's
gonna strike here.
Don't lie to me.
If you know something I want you to tell
me, why are you trying to get rid of me?
But I'm not.
It's just like that guy gathering
a bunch of small timers.
But thanks to that, this robbery's
gonna turn into quite the show.
oh,
oh, oh.
Oh, oh,
It's Ganobad!
Amelia!
It's too early in the
morning for this crap.
This sucker's not being able to buy.
300 million double dollars!
It's not happening!
We're business!
You don't stand a chance!
This is my better day! Move it! He's mine!
Gas backs hit the front gate!
Oh, damn it.
My head is killing me.
He's actually here, Meryl.
What do we do?
I can only think of one thing.
We'll protect that brawn statue.
What?
We're really gonna do it?
What's up? Ah!
Ah!
Oh! Oh, my God.
Come on here!
You guys are going to pay for this!
That's what I think about that!
Uh, Meryl?
Everybody, listen up!
We can't let him lay one
finger on this bronze statue!
Or I'll be with me!
Who's that? Daniel? It's
him! Come out of here!
But we're supposed to guard this gate!
What about our contract?
Cain!
Are you sure we're gonna be okay?
Don't you think it would be better
if we just split town all together?
Shut up!
My assets aren't small like yours.
I can't just leave them behind
and run off into the desert
Small, do you have any clue how much
money I invested in that cargo hovercraft?
It was a fortune Stop talking!
He's coming for revenge.
This is payback for what
we did to him 20 years ago
He'll take it all.
Everything I've built.
All of it gone?
So you're the one who's been getting
in my way a little bit at a time.
What?
A little bit at a time?
I thought I tried harder than that.
Sorry, but the roads closed this way
So it's you you're gonna get
mixed up in this again, huh?
I don't quite get what's
going on, but here I come.
If it's possible, maybe you wouldn't mind
just turning around and leaving town?
I've got business with someone inside.
Does business mean killing this guy?
You could say that.
Then no, I can't let you go through!
You're gonna have to let him pass.
Huh?
Wolfwood?
Needlenoggin.
You're gonna have to
give an inch on this one.
At what point did you change
your religion to robbery?
Don't be an idiot.
I'm doing this out of my
obligation to my word.
Now move!
Seriously, I can't move.
It's like I'm stuck here.
This isn't funny.
Do it.
This stinks.
My contract's complete.
He's here.
You bastard!
Listen, Gasback, everything
that's happened is their fault.
Everything, even the crap
we pulled 20 years ago.
Please!
Look, I punished them for
you, so just spare me!
Don't kill me!
Please, please, please!
Please!
Shut up.
I always knew you were an
irredeemable piece of filth,
but growing older has just made you worse.
You're beyond help now.
Oh, God, no!
Don't do it!
Please don't kill me!
Hold it right there
Dashback! Amelia?
I've got you, it's over You think?
You got a lot of spirit in you, girl
It's gotten quiet out here.
Don't tell me it's over!
That it looks like everything
worked out for the best?
Come on, don't be so
blindly optimistic, Millie.
Keep your guard up, right?
I wouldn't try it, lady?
You'll get hurt!
Move.
That technique of yours
isn't going to work on me.
Really?
You sound pretty confident.
But if you wanted to kill me,
you should have shot me from
behind without wasting your breath.
Because now you've left me an opportunity.
Time out.
Could you give us some time to catch up?
It's been a while since we talked.
What?
It's been what, 20 years since
we ran into each other last Mr.
Gasback?
Except for a few minutes ago,
wow, a stickler for details,
you're still Farting
around like a fool, I see.
Want to tell me how it is you look
the same as You did 20 years ago,
I'm young at heart.
Gas back is gonna get away
to let go of my gun no
way pull your finger out
or I'm pulling the trigger.
Sorry.
No
Ash one thing
What's up?
Are you trying to save me like
you did 20 years ago in that bank?
Man who would think the humanoid
typhoon has a soft spot?
Humanoid typhoon don't tell me you're!
It was you.
You were the accomplice.
Now Vash didn't I explain to you in a
world built on struggles you don't give!
I don't believe it's smart to give
anything not even a single life.
You think the guy you just tossed
will turn out to be a lucky one?
Don't know see ya stop.
So, he got away.
I can't believe you were
the jerk from 20 years ago!
Why?
Why did you do something like that?
You were like that when
I met you the first time
and you pulled the same
crap again at the bar!
Is it some kind of religious thing?
No, not at all.
But they're all alive right now.
Why change that?
Listen up!
You might think it's cute going around
saving people's lives in your light-hearted,
righteous way,
but have you ever thought about it?
When you save someone like Gaspak, he
just goes out there and kills more people!
People who wouldn't have had to die,
who wouldn't have had to suffer!
People like...
people like my mother!
I'm going to kill Gasback.
Nothing's going to stop me.
So you're being a pain in
the ass as usual, I see.
What can I do about it?
It's my nature to be who I am.
I'm the one who threw the die on this one.
And you do have the
worst throw in the world.
I'm not giving this
place up to that bastard.
Twenty years of my
blood, sweat, and tears.
We'll see about that.
Cave!
Killing you wouldn't
be near enough to make
up for what you took
from me twenty years ago,
not even close, and you know it.
I want to make this even.
I have to take everything from you.
It's time to show you the greatest
robbery in the history of the world
Are you insane Marshall?
Why do you have us tied up?
Kane really worked my ass into
the ground these last few years.
What?
I may not have been Marshall
too long, but I had my fun
What did you do?
What did you do to my plan?
Shut your mouth and watch the show.
Our plans, Dale. Our town.
You see that?
Yes, I do.
What the hell? It's rolling!
So, uh, have any ideas on
what we should do next?
Yes, I do.
What else do you think?
We've run like the wind!
Because where there's
life, there's hope, right?
Damn, that was close.
And it's not even broken.
The five billion double dollars!
That's the face, Kane!
That's the face I wanted to see you make!
You made a disgrace of my
robbery a long time ago,
and today you're paying the price.
Yo, boss!
Let's blow this town!
Our power plant, we're
never gonna see it again.
You really just stole our
plants away, so this is why?
Stole the cargo craft!
It's all over for this town!
Needle noggin, wait, he won't get away!
Move it or I'll run you!
Jeez, you suck!
Could you drive better?
You know I'm a lousy driver!
I'm doing my best now, Leon!
Let me drive, would you?
Not a chance!
Oh, no! Look out ahead!
Let's go!
Stop!
If you end up breaking the
plant, there's no way to fix it!
Castback escaping's a bigger problem!
Now move!
Move your ass! Don't shoot him!
You're nuts!
Stop! Don't do it!
You can't shoot him!
Get out of the freaking way!
Don't you screw with me either!
I'm not trying to!
Amelia!
Pull your head!
Watch out!
Needle-noggin! Needle-noggin!
Here!
Hang on, Needle-noggin!
No!
How?
I don't get it.
He knew he was about to die.
How could he have looked so calm about it?
How?
It looked like he was
thinking, what can you do?
What's that mean?
Explain it to me.
He's telling me not to kill anyone,
but it's okay for him to die?
Nothing about that's right.
My mother died because he saved gas
back but it wasn't just my mom who
had to suffer because of that there
are so many people others in the world
who wouldn't have had to go through
hell if Vash hadn't saved gas back
so he rescues someone from a situation
when he didn't have to and this is
what he gets?
Seriously, I don't understand this at all.
Is there any point to it?
Vash
is dead.
And for what?
All your fancy words.
All your ideals.
They're all over the second
you die.
I know.
And I feel let down. Seriously.
Maybe he thought if he tossed
a die and put up a struggle,
that a decent point to
it all might surface.
But, like you were saying, once he's
dead, he can't cast that die anymore.
So what's the point of the whole thing?
It's hot out here.
Nothing in town works without the plans.
Our electricity's gone.
How long is our water going to last?
With no heater, the old folks
at my place are going to die.
Everybody calm down.
Now, we've asked the
neighboring town for some help,
and we're considering renting a plan.
Great, but we're having trouble now.
I know you are but water comes first
and we can't get water without a plan.
One of my kids just had surgery
and his breathing machine
stopped working my husband's
pumping it manually right now?
I never thought he'd go so low
as a steal on power supply.
We keep running like this
the whole town will collapse
Stop if you end up breaking the
plant There's no way to fix it!
Gas-back escaping's a bigger problem!
Now move!
I can't believe it.
I'm not any different from Gas-back, am I?
That idiot.
What is that, Mom?
It's a precious secret, sweetie.
What kind of secret?
The kind I'll tell you about someday
when you grow up to be a young woman.
Amelia, I'm sorry, baby.
I'm sorry I won't be able to be.
I won't be.
I won't be with you as you grow up.
That precious secret.
Do you remember?
I'll tell you now.
Mom! Mom!
What is it?
Tell me! Mom!
Mom!
We've got a report back to headquarters
about the end of bash the stampede,
so move it all redhead
Whoa, Meryl, are you alright?
you're gas backs bodyguard
aren't you my contract expired
I'm a free agent so you
maybe want to be hired by me
you're really going to do it
huh why do you share Vash's
principles give me every bit
of cash you've got as an advance
Also, I want you to throw in breakfast.
It's against all of my
principles to skip breakfast.
Hey, boss!
The bodyguard fella.
And he's brought that
chick along with him.
Cotsie's showing up just the two of them.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Ahhhh!
Knock to the left and run
towards where I shoot.
Yeah, I gotcha.
One, two, three! Go!
He's over there!
Now what?
You're missing me on purpose, aren't you?
I thought you came out here to kill me.
Whatever.
You want to keep this dance swirling?
Fine.
The plant's going back with me. It's what?
And freeze.
In a world where you take
and have things taken,
lady you tried to rob a
robber that takes balls!
I'm guessing you won't
have much of a problem
with me taking your life away from you?
Then you made a disgrace
of my robbery, bitch!
Glad to see you back, buddy.
This is it for you.
I'm sorry
It's too bad I hate to do this
Good night, pal.
Say, the hell?
You're going full of blanks or what?
I shot him.
I know I did.
Amelia!
Are you all right?
Bud, you're doing kind
of a sloppy job here.
I mean, what was your plan
if my sweet Amelia got hurt?
Can we start with how you're not dead?
Yeah, I thought I was a goner
too, but check this sucker out.
Hard Smoke Thomas sure is a hell of a ration
to keep on you while you're traveling.
Of course, the insurance
girls happened to pass by.
I almost died. You bastard.
I'll take this out of your ass.
Later. What?
You're not happy I'm alive?
Maybe I'll beat your ass right now.
That doesn't sound like fun.
So, I think maybe it's time
we end this whole thing,
because if we continue
on, it'll be a real pain.
All right, Vash.
I want to settle up with you.
What? Right here? Be quiet.
I'll leave this place right
after I finally kill you.
Let's find out the verdict
on that die you cast.
Wolfwood.
I don't want you to jump into this always
trying to steal the spotlight Amelia?
This ain't a duel we go
when this hits the ground!
Oh, my God.
Oh, no,
no,
no.
I don't know.
You're a lot stronger than him.
I can finally see now that
the legend of the humanoid
typhoon isn't based solely
on the devil's luck.
Yeah.
I guess I owe you an apology
for what I did, don't I?
Right.
If you hadn't saved Gaz back, my
mom might have lived a long life.
But that's the way things worked out.
I'm sorry. I am.
It's not over. It's...
not over. No, wait.
I am going to
take your life.
What the?
You have you have one of
the gloves where did you get
that glove tell me Now that I
made it and gave it to my mom
You gave it to her, and
she, in turn, gave it to me.
It was 20 years ago you
gave this thing to her.
You remember?
That...
that makes you...
After you left her behind, my mother
gave birth to me without anyone's help.
Her life was a hard one. But how?
I gave her enough money to live
comfortably for the rest of her days.
Because someone like you came
through and took it away!
Took everything!
No one would help Gaspak's
wife and daughter.
They hated us.
Did she die?
Of course.
The doctor wouldn't even see her.
So she...
she gave this to you?
She never told me the reason why.
She never had time.
Not like this.
That's not how you would have
wanted this to end, is it, Mom?
Not shooting a man in cold blood.
Maybe this means I cast a die, too.
Guess I can't make fun of you, can I?
Gas back!
I'm not gonna let you get
away with this you bastard!
I can't live my life until I kill you.
Deader than dead he's still alive!
This guy's getting on my nerves?
Have any idea what he wants!
Now whoa that designs weird!
I'll
make sure
everyone dies!
I'll wipe out every one of you.
except for myself.
Hey, Needlenoggin, hey!
Bye.
You doing okay up there?
I'm good, so the next one up.
She didn't have to give all the
money to the town, you know.
She couldn't pass me off a bonus or
a contingency fee, don't you think?
It's your own fault.
You didn't put it in the contract.
You had rights to have that
bounty money, too, man.
Why'd you turn it down?
Because going to the police
always leads to trouble somehow.
And trust me, you don't
want to depend on my wallet.
But I still have to.
And hey, if I'm walking around with part
of $60 billion double dollars in my pocket,
There's a lot less possibility I'll
have to be an errand boy for a robber.
Listen, Wolfwood, do you mind
not walking so close to me?
It's so cold sometimes.
Excuse me, boys, but
we gotta run on ahead.
Gotta get our tails back
to headquarters ASAP.
Turns out we don't have to pay the insurance
money for the bronze statue at all.
No kidding?
That's excellent.
With a criminal making the contract out
under a false name, it's null and void now.
Pretty sweet.
Now we can report to headquarters
as two proud insurance agents.
They're so damn cheerful.
Come with me.
I can offer you protection.
Thank you, but I can't go with a robber.
I will accept this, though.
I suppose if I return it, my
connection to you will be cut, right?
And then, the next time we meet...
She'd meet me.
Say, did you have any idea that
Amelia was only around 19 years old?
Yeah, I had my guess that
she was in that age range.
What I'm getting at is if you hadn't saved
Gaspak, she never would have been born.
It's about the shape of it.
Makes sense.
Must mean you don't always
get a bad roll of the dice,
even when it turns up snake eyes.
Yeah.
Where do you think you're going?
The town we're going to just that way.
Wait a second!
Show me that paper.
Hey!
That's mine!
The Dodongo Brothers who were given a
270 year sentence busted out of jail.
Wait, don't tell me.
Did you have something to do with this?
Please tell me you're not wrapped
up with bad guys like them.
Well, are you or not? Answer me! Hello?
What did you do with them?
Can you even hear me?
Hey, wait!